all right how much disk space do you
need for your Linux virtual machine I
put 100 gigabytes the default is usually
20 the reason I put 100 is because we
are going to be
using uh dis storage by the way don't do
the one do the one where it
incrementally
grows um and we'll go through that whole
thing but the reason that it's 100 is
because we are going to be doing
container stuff the reason we're using a
virtual machine at all is so that you
can run um things like mini Cube and
Docker and and and all you know podman
and all of the tools for doing
containerization and playing around with
containers as soon as you start doing
any amount of
containers um inside of a virtual
machine um you start to run into the
disc space limitations otherwise I would
normally say 20 you know 20 Gigabytes is
plenty for a virtual machine